<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IndianFestival</string>
    <string name="about_diwali">Diwali, Deepavali or Dipavali is the Hindu festival of lights,
        which is celebrated every autumn in the northern hemisphere (spring in southern hemisphere).
        One of the most popular festivals of Hinduism, Diwali symbolises the spiritual "victory of light
        over darkness, good over evil and knowledge over ignorance." Light is a metaphor for
        knowledge and consciousness.During the celebration, temples, homes, shops and office
        buildings are brightly illuminated.The preparations, and rituals, for the festival
        typically last five days, with the climax occurring on the third day coinciding with
        the darkest night of the Hindu lunisolar month Kartika. In the Gregorian calendar,the
        festival generally falls between mid-October and mid-November.</string>
    <string name="about_eid">Eid al-Fitr is an important religious holiday celebrated by Muslims
        worldwide that marks the end of Ramadan, the Islamic holy month of fasting (sawm).
        This religious Eid (Muslim religious festival) is the first and only day in the month
        of Shawwal during which Muslims are not permitted to fast. The holiday celebrates the
        conclusion of the 29 or 30 days of dawn-to-sunset fasting during the entire month of
        Ramadan. The day of Eid, therefore, falls on the first day of the month of Shawwal.
        The date for the start of any lunar Hijri month varies based on when the new moon is
        sighted by local religious authorities, so the exact day of celebration varies by locality.</string>
    <string name="about_holi">Holi is a Hindu spring festival, originating from India, celebrated
        predominantly in India but has also spread to Nepal and many other Western countries,
        also known as the "festival of colours" or the "festival of love".The festival signifies
        the victory of good over evil, the arrival of spring, end of winter, and for many a
        festive day to meet others, play and laugh, forget and forgive, and repair broken relationships.
        It is also celebrated as a thanksgiving for a good harvest.It lasts for a night and a day,
        starting on the evening of the Purnima (Full Moon day) falling in the Vikram Samvat Hindu
        Calendar month of Phalgun, which falls somewhere between the end of February
        and the middle of March in the Gregorian calendar. </string>
    <string name="about_pola">pola is mainly a farmer festival, wherein farmers respect their bulls and
        oxe, to thank them for their support in farming. It occurs after the monsoon sowing and field work,
        typically in late August or early September. On the day of Pola, the bulls are first given a bath,
        and then decorated with ornaments and shawls. Their horns are painted, and their necks are adorned with
        garlands of flowers. The bulls do not work that day, and they are part of procession where farmers
        celebrate the crop season.
    </string>
    <string name="about_christmas">Christmas is an annual festival commemorating the birth of Jesus Christ,observed
    primarily on December 25 as a religious and cultural celebration among billions of
    people around the world.A feast central to the Christian liturgical year, it is preceded
    by the season of Advent or the Nativity Fast and initiates the season of Christmastide,
    which historically in the West lasts twelve days and culminates on Twelfth Night;in some
    traditions, Christmastide includes an octave.Christmas Day is a public holiday in many
    of the world's nations,is celebrated religiously by a majority of Christians,as well as
    culturally by many non-Christians,and forms an integral part of the holiday season centered around it.
    </string>
    <string name="about_gudipadwa">Gudhi Padva is a spring-time festival that marks the traditional
        new year for Marathi Hindus.It is celebrated in and near Maharashtra on the first day of
        the Chaitra month to mark the beginning of the New year according to the lunisolar Hindu
        calendar. The word padva comes from the Sanskrit word प्रतिपदा (pratipadā)in Sanskrit, which
        refers to the first day of a lunar fortnight. The festival is observed with colorful floor
        decorations called rangoli, a special Gudhi flag (garlanded with flowers, mango and neem leaves,
        topped with upturned silver or copper vessel), street processions, dancing and festive foods.
    </string>
    <string name="about_navratri">Navaratri also spelled Navratri or Navarathri, is a nine nights (and ten days) Hindu
    festival, celebrated in the Tamil month of Purattasi (17th September to 17th October) every year.
    It is celebrated differently in various parts of the Indian subcontinent.[3][1] There are two
    seasonal Navaratri in a year. This festival in this month is called Sharada Navaratri that is
    the most celebrated for Goddess Durga.In India, Goddess Durga battles and emerges victorious
        over the buffalo demon Mahishasuran to help restore Dharma.Celebrations include stage
        decorations, recital of the legend, enacting of the story, and chanting of the scriptures of Hinduism.
    </string>
    <string name="about_sankranti">Makara Sankranti, also known as Makaraa Sankrānti or Maghi,
        is a festival day in the Hindu calendar, in reference to deity Surya (sun). It is observed
        each year in January.It marks the first day of sun is transit into the Makara (Capricorn),
        marking the end of the month with the winter solstice and the start of longer days.Makara
        Sankranti is one of the few ancient Indian festivals that has been observed according
        to solar cycles, while most festivals are set by the lunar cycle of the lunisolar Hindu calendar.
    </string>
</resources>
